W. R. "Bob" Poage Campaign papers, Inclusive: 1898-1997, undated, Bulk: 1936-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
W. R. "Bob" Poage Campaign papers
Inclusive: 1898-1997, undated, Bulk: 1936-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
1E
Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899 - 1987
58 document boxes and 1 oversized box.
The W. R. "Bob" Poage Campaign papers consist of materials produced during the political campaigns of Bob Poage, primarily as the U.S. Representative for the Eleventh Congressional District of Texas from 1937 to 1978. The collection includes correspondence, financial documents, subject files, and promotional materials relating to his campaigns in Central Texas as well as the broader changes affecting the Democratic Party in the mid-twentieth century.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
William Robert “Bob” Poage, the son of William Allen Poage and Helen Wheeler Conger, was born on December 28, 1899, in Waco, Texas. The Poage family moved to Throckmorton County shortly thereafter where William A. Poage worked as a rancher and cattleman. The Poages eventually returned to Waco in 1913. Five years later, in 1918, Poage graduated from Waco High School and joined the U.S. Navy as an apprentice seaman during the waning months of World War I.
After the war, Poage briefly attended classes at the University of Texas and the University of Colorado at Boulder before enrolling at Baylor University. In 1921, he graduated with a bachelor’s degree in geology. Poage taught geology from 1922 to 1924, while simultaneously working on his law degree. In 1924, he earned his law degree from Baylor University and gained admittance to the Texas Bar.
In that same year, Poage ran for political office, winning a seat in the Texas House of Representatives. He served in the Texas House from 1925 to 1929, all while practicing law in Waco and teaching at Baylor Law School. In 1928, Poage attempted but lost a bid for a seat in the Texas Senate and briefly returned to civilian life. In 1931, Poage sought to fill a Senate seat vacated by Edgar Witt. He won the special election this time, ultimately serving in the Texas Senate from 1931 to 1937.
Striving to increase his political influence, Poage tried to unseat U.S. Representative O.H. Cross of the Eleventh Congressional District of Texas. Poage lost in 1934 but succeeded in defeating Cross in 1936. It was to be the start of a long-tenured career for the Texas Democrat. On February 14, 1938, amidst his political successes, Poage married Frances Lenoir Cotton.
Poage served in the U.S. House from 1937 until his retirement in 1978, often running unopposed in the biennial elections. Drawing from his childhood experiences and education, Poage championed life in rural America, seeking improvements such as water and telephone services and helping to establish the Rural Electrification Administration. Often referred to as “Mr. Agriculture”, Poage was a key member of the House Agriculture Committee from 1941 to 1978, chairing the committee from 1967 to 1974. Upon his retirement from the House in 1978, Poage was succeeded by Democrat Marvin Leath.
The W. R. Poage Legislative Library was opened in September 1979 in honor of Representative Poage and serves as the repository for his personal and congressional papers. Poage wrote five books during his lifetime including three in retirement: After the Pioneers (1969), Politics-Texas Style (1974), How We Lived (1980), McLennan County Before 1980 (1981), and his autobiography, My First 85 Years (1985).
Poage passed away during open-heart surgery in Temple, Texas, on January 3, 1987, and is buried in Waco’s Oakwood Cemetery.
Scope and Content
The collection's inclusive date range covers nearly one hundred years of history (1898 to 1997) but the bulk of the materials stem from Congressman Bob Poage's career as a U.S. Representative (1937 to 1978).
Files from the late 1930's detail Poage's rise to prominence and his early years in the U.S. House of Representatives. Much of the materials focus on O.H. Cross, Poage's predecessor from the Eleventh District of Texas, as well as the effects the New Deal was having on Poage's constituents.
Materials from the 1940's relate to World War II and Poage's hope for neutrality prior to the attack on Pearl Harbor. In addition to Poage's budding friendship with fellow Texan Lyndon B. Johnson, these years also reflect changes in the Democratic Party, particularly in members from the Southern states. The late 1940's and the early 1950's reflect the prominent issues of the day such as Civil Rights and communism.
The 1960's attest to Poage's friendships with and support of President John F. Kennedy and his successor Lyndon Johnson. The 1970's, Poage's final decade in Washington, D.C., focus on the Nixon Administration, the addition of new counties into the Eleventh Congressional District, and tough political opposition in candidates such as Murray Watson, Jack Burgess, and Lane Denton. The scope of the collection concludes with Poage's retirement in 1978 and his careful monitoring of the election that year, a race won by Marvin Leath.
Arrangement
The W. R. “Bob” Poage papers have been processed previously, most notably in 1995. Detailed finding aids and folder listings existed prior to this latest round of processing.
Due to the large size of the collection, the W. R. “Bob” Poage papers have been divided into six new collections based on the existing series outline. The documents in the Campaign papers were originally housed in boxes #1381-1420 and boxes #1577-1578. Some loose materials have also been integrated with these files.
This collection is now arranged according to material type. In the past, these materials were divided into Correspondence Files and Reference Files. The latter section has been renamed “Subject Files”, and two other series have been created due to the prevalence of financial and promotional materials. Thus, the collection is currently arranged into four series: I. Correspondence, II. Financial Documents, III. Subject Files, and IV. Promotional Materials.
There are two arrangement schemes present in this collection. Series I. Correspondence and Series II. Financial Documents are arranged chronologically by year. Series III. Subject Files and Series IV. Promotional Materials are organized alphabetically by topic or type of material.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 1E. Acquired 1961-08-01
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Mattie Mae McKee papers, Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
W. R. "Bob" Poage Texas Development papers, Inclusive: 1913-1979, undated, Bulk: 1946-1978
William Robert "Bob" Poage Papers
Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
W. R. "Bob" Poage State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1923-1971, undated, Bulk: 1933-1936
W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1838-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Related references
Duggan, Laura Woolsey. “Poage, William Robert.” Handbook of Texas Online, accessed June 11, 2019.
Pearson, Richard. “Former U.S. Rep. William R. (Bob) Poage Dies.” Washington Post, January 4, 1987.
Poage, W. R. My First 85 Years. Waco, TX: Texian Press, 1985.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Burgess, Jack (Politician); Cross, O.H. (Oliver Harlan),1868-1960.; Denton, Lane.; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald),1917-1963.; Leath, James Marvin, 1931-2000.; Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899-1987.; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing),1900-1965.; Tirey, Frank.; Watson, Murray, Jr.,1932-2018.
Subjects (Organizations)
United States. Congress -- Constituent communication.; United States. Congress. House -- Elections.; United States. Congress. House -- Records and correspondence.
Subjects
Political campaigns -- Texas -- McLennan County.; Political campaigns -- Texas.
Genres
Photo negative; Postcards; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Election returns.; Ephemera.; Financial records.; Photographs.; Promotional materials.; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Correspondence, 1936-1978; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I. Correspondence, the largest series in the collection, spans the entirety of Bob Poage's career in the U.S. House of Representatives, from his election in 1936 to his retirement in 1978. The majority of the folders are divided between correspondence with constituents, colleagues, Democratic campaign committees, and individuals or organizations from out-of-district. Folder organization changes with Poage's rising prominence in Congress and in the Democratic Party, shifting from mostly district and colleague correspondence to a wider range of topics and correspondents and a closer connection to national Democratic campaigns. The materials in this series are arranged chronologically and are in good condition.
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1936 Campaign (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Congratulations, First Congressional Election (1 of 2), 1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Congratulations, First Congressional Election (2 of 2), 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District, Postmaster General Visit, James Farley, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Colleagues and Democratic National Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1940 Campaign, Original Letters, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Announcement for Re-Election, 1938 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District, Local Opposition (1 of 3), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - District, Local Opposition (2 of 3), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - District, Local Opposition (3 of 3), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1940 Campaign, Concerning O.H. Cross, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - District, American Neutrality, Local Opposition, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - L.C. Alexander, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - White House, Eleanor Roosevelt Visit to Waco, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campaign, General (1 of 5), 1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Campaign, General (2 of 5), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, General (3 of 5), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, General (4 of 5), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Campaign, General (5 of 5), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Campaign, Bell County (1 of 3), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Campaign, Bell County (2 of 3), 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, Bell County (3 of 3), 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, Coryell County, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Campaign, Falls County, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Campaign, Milam County, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, Endorsement Letters, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1940 Campaign, James McAlexander (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Management, Clarence Elwell, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1940 Campaign, Myrtle Taylor (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1940 Campaign, Outgoing Letters (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1940 Campaign, Picnics (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1940 Campaign, Scott Poage (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - L.C. Alexander, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Letter Campaign #1, McLennan County (1 of 4), 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Letter Campaign #1, McLennan County (2 of 4), 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Letter Campaign #1, McLennan County (3 of 4), 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Letter Campaign #1, McLennan County (4 of 4), 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Letter Campaign #2, McLennan County (1 of 5), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Letter Campaign #2, McLennan County (2 of 5), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Letter Campaign #2, McLennan County (3 of 5), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Letter Campaign #2, McLennan County (4 of 5), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Letter Campaign #2, McLennan County (5 of 5), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Letter Campaign #3, McLennan County (1 of 4), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Letter Campaign #3, McLennan County (2 of 4), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Letter Campaign #3, McLennan County (3 of 4), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Letter Campaign #3, McLennan County (4 of 4), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Letter Campaign #2, Bosque County (1 of 3), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Letter Campaign #2, Bosque County (2 of 3), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Letter Campaign #2, Bosque County (3 of 3), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1940 Campaign, Responses to Letters Poage Sent, 1940 May-July (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1940 Campaign, Announcements to Campaign Managers, 1940 June-July (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1940 Campaign, Mailed Hand Card, 1940 June-July (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1940 Campaign, Placards, 1940 June-July (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1940 Campaign, Precinct Contacts, 1940 July (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for Lyndon B. Johnson, Senate, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - District, War, General, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - District, War, Campaign, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Campaign, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - District, Campaign, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Carlton J., 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Austin, Texas, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Axtell, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Bartlett, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Belton, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ben Arnold, Texas, 1942-1945 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Buckholts and Burlington, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Calvert, Texas, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cameron, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Clifton, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cranfills Gap and Crawford, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Eddy, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Elm Mott and Evant, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Gause, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Gatesville, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Highbank, Texas, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Holland, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Iredell, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ireland, Texas, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jonesboro, Texas, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Killeen, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Kopperl, Texas, 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lerox, Levite, and Little River, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lorena, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Loft, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - McGregor, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Marlin, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Mart, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Maysfield, Texas, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Meridian, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Milano, Texas, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Moody, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Morgan, Texas, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Oglesby, Texas, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Purmela, Reagan, and Riesel, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rockdale, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Rogers, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Rosebud, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Ross and Satin, Texas, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Temple, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Thorndale, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Troy and Turnersville, Texas, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Valley Mills, Texas, 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Waco, Texas (1 of 2), 1942-1948 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Waco, Texas (2 of 2), 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Wichita Falls, Texas, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - West, Texas, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Walnut Springs, Texas, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - A, District, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - B, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - C, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - D, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - E, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - F, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - G, District, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - H, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - I, District, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - J, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - K, District, 1942-1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - L, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Mc, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - M, District, 1942-1948 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - N, District, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - O, District, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - P, District, 1942-1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - R, District, 1942-1948 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - S, District, 1942-1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - T, District, 1942-1948 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - U, District, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - V, District, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - W, District, 1942-1948 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Y-Z, District, 1942-1946 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - District, General, 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1944 Campaign (1 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1944 Campaign (2 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1944 Campaign (3 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1944 Campaign (4 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Plunkett Contested Election Letter, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - District, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Campaign, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Poage Day Dinner (1 of 2), 1948 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Poage Day Dinner (2 of 2), 1948 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1950 Campaign, Concerning Advertisements (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1950 Campaign, Form Letters (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - A-B, District, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - C, District, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - D, District, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - E-G, District, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - H, District, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - I-L, District, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - M-N, District, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - O-R, District, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - S, District (1 of 2), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - S, District (2 of 2), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - T-Z, District, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bell County, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bosque County, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Coryell County, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Falls County, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - McLennan County, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Milam County, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Campaign (1 of 2), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Campaign (2 of 2), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - District, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Campaign (1 of 2), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Campaign (2 of 2), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Party Politics, Elections, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Personal, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Senate Race Opening, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Party Politics, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Campaign, Unopposed Primary, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Colleagues, Elections, Party Politics, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Party Politics, Political Issues, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, Election Returns, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention, Chicago, Illinois, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - District, Political Issues, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Party Politics, Elections, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Election, Adlai Stevenson, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - District, Speaking Engagement, Advertisements, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - District, Special Election (Senate), Party Politics, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, Newspaper Announcement Requests, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Colleagues, Democratic Committees, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - District, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Out of District, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Colleagues, Democratic Committees, and Presidential Nominees, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - District, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Out of District, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Campaign, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - District, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - John F. Kennedy’s and Lyndon B. Johnson's Visit to Waco, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Out of District, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - President Harry Truman's Visit to Waco, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Nominees, Kennedy/Johnson Campaign, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Agriculture, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Colleagues, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - District, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Out of District, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Campaign, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - District, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Out of District, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - District, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Out of District, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Campaign (1 of 6), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Campaign (2 of 6), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Campaign (3 of 6), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Campaign (4 of 6), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Campaign (5 of 6), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Campaign (6 of 6), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - District, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Out of District, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Campaign, Johnson/Humphrey campaign, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - District, Redistricting, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Out of District, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Campaign (1 of 4), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Campaign (2 of 4), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Campaign (3 of 4), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Campaign (4 of 4), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - District, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Out of District, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - District, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Out of District, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Campaign (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Campaign (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Campaign (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - District, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Out of District, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1968 Election, Presidential Candidates (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1970 Campaign, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - District, Poage Appreciation Dinner, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Out of District, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Campaign (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Campaign (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - District, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - District, Student Research Paper Requests, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Out of District, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1972 Campaign (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1972 Campaign (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Campaign, Advertising, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Granbury, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Rockdale, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Taylor, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Temple, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Weatherford, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Waco (1 of 4), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Waco (2 of 4), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Waco (3 of 4), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)